RG 005:026, Office of the Governor: Wilbur L. Cross (1931-1939)
Connecticut State Library
Wilbur L. Cross records
1931-1939
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Governor (1931-1939: Cross)
53.25 cubic feet
Gov. Wilbur L. Cross's correspondence and subject files.
RG005_026
T001169
Biographical Note
Born: April 10, 1862, Mansfield, Connecticut.
College: Yale, 1885; Yale Ph.D., 1889.
Political Party: Democrat.
Offices: Governor of Connecticut, 1931-1939.
Died: October 5, 1948, New Haven, Connecticut.
The Republicans' hold on the office of governor in Connecticut came to an end in 1931 when Wilbur Cross was inaugurated. Cross seemed to be the opposite of one who could unseat anyone, much less an entrenched political force. He was 68 years old, just retired from Yale, and had never held an elected public position before. Cross had grown up in Mansfield where his family did farming and some manufacturing. He worked at times at a local store. In 1885 he graduated from Yale and four years later earned his doctorate degree there. Cross spent several years as a high school principal and schoolteacher, but in 1894 he was made a professor of English at Yale. Over the next 36 years he taught at Yale, became editor of the Yale Review, and made Dean of the Yale Graduate School. In 1889 he married Helen Avery and they had two children.
When Cross retired from Yale in 1930 he had never held a public office. He did, however, belong to an informal group of Yale men and New Haven personalities that met weekly. Here, Cross often presented his political views in dramatic fashion and when the distraught Democratic party in the state was seeking a gubernatorial candidate to run against the strong Republican machine, Cross was pushed for the honor by New Haven's Democrats. Nominated at the state convention, Cross used his country humor and personality to help defeat the Republican candidate. He especially pushed for repeal of Prohibition. He was the only Democrat to win a state office that year, but as the Great Depression continued into the decade the Democrats eventually gained control of the government. Cross was reelected three times and served a total of eight years, the first to do so since the 1860's.
Even though the Republicans controlled the General Assembly during his early terms, Cross was able to work with it to achieve some programs to help the unemployed. He eventually adopted the New Deal programs of President Franklin Roosevelt. During one violent strike in Connecticut he personally used his position as governor to bring management and labor together. By 1937 Cross enjoyed a Democratic General Assembly and was able to have his reorganization plan for state government implemented. One of its goals was to create a merit system for state employment rather than through political patronage. Cross presided over the state's observance of its 300th anniversary - the Tercentenary Celebration. He also had to deal with two major disasters during his terms. One was the 1936 flood and the second was the 1938 Hurricane. While previous twentieth century governors had used the office as an honorary position as much as an administrative one, Cross made it a full time job and worked at being governor even when the Legislature was not in session.
Cross ran for reelection in 1938, but a rejuvenated Republican party was able to defeat him. A heavy vote for the third party candidacy of Jasper McLevy took away some of his former support at the polls. Cross continued his work of research and writing, but did not abandon his thoughts of political office. He tried to get his party's nomination for governor in 1940, but lost to Robert Hurley, who did go on to win the position. In 1946, at the age of 84, Cross ran for the unexpired term of U.S. Senator and was defeated by Governor Raymond Baldwin. Two years later Cross-died. The Mansfield Historical Society owns the home where he was born, but a house nearby where he later lived is privately owned. His house in New Haven where he lived while working at Yale and when governor still stands and it is privately owned. Schools in New Haven and Bridgeport are named in his honor, as is the Wilbur Cross parkway. The former library building on the campus of the University of Connecticut in Storrs still bears his name.
Bibliography
Congressional Quarterly's Guide to United States Elections. Washington, D.C.: Congressional Quarterly, 1994. [CSL call number GIS Ref JK 1967 .C662 1994.]
Crofut, Florence S. Marcy. Guide to the History and the Historic Sites of Connecticut. New Haven, Conn.: Yale University Press, 1937. [CSL call number HistRef F 94 .C88 1937].
Cross, Wilbur Lucius. Connecticut Yankee: Autobiography. New Haven, Conn.: Yale University Press, 1943.
Davidson, Eugene A. "A Cross for Connecticut." Outlook and Independent, CLVII, January 14, 1931.
Glashan, Roy R. American Governors and Gubernatorial Elections, 1775-1975. Stillwater, Minn.: Croixside Press, 1975. [CSL call number JK 2447 .G53 1975].
Marsh, William John. The Man With a Million Friends, Wilbur L. Cross. New Milford, Conn.: Marsh Bros., 1934.
Murray, Sister Mary. "Connecticut's Depression Governor: Wilbur L. Cross." Connecticut History 16 (August 1975), pp. 44-64.
Sobel, Robert and John Raimo. Biographical Directory of the Governors of the United States, 1789-1978. Westport, Conn.: Meckler Books, 1978. [CSL call number GIS Ref E 176 .B573].
Van Dusen, Albert E. Connecticut. New York: Random House, 1961. [CSL call number HistRef F 94 .V3].
Woodbury, Robert L. "Wilbur Cross: New Deal Ambassador to a Yankee Culture." New England Quarterly 41 (September, 1968) 3:323-40.
Scope and Content
Gov. Wilbur L. Cross's records are correspondence and subject files related to state agencies, commissions, legislative bills, and appointments among other topics.
Arrangement
Series 1. Correspondence
Series 2. Subject Files.
Subseries 1. 1931-1933.
Subseries 2. 1933-1935.
Subseries 3. 1935-1937.
Subseries 4. 1937-1939.
Series 3. Place cards.
Related Material
None.
Index Terms
Persons:
Cross, Wilbur L. (Wilbur Lucius), 1862-1948
Subjects:
Cross, Wilbur L. (Wilbur Lucius), 1862-1948 -- Archives; Connecticut. Office of the Governor -- Archives; Connecticut -- History -- Sources; Connecticut -- Politics and government -- 1865-1950 -- Sources; Governors -- Connecticut -- Archives
Document Types:
Correspondence; Political cartoons; Records
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Correspondence, 1931-1939; T001169
  - A-M, 1931-1932 (Box 364)
  - N-Z, 1931-1932 (Box 365)
  - A-H, 1933-1934 (Box 366)
  - I-N, 1933-1934 (Box 367)
  - N-S, 1933-1934 (Box 368)
  - S-Z, 1933-1934 (Box 369)
  - A-D, 1935-1936 (Box 370)
  - E-K, 1935-1936 (Box 371)
  - L-O, 1935-1936 (Box 372)
  - P-V, 1935-1936 (Box 373)
  - W-Z, 1935-1936 (Box 373a)
  - A-C, 1937-1939 (Box 374)
  - D-J, 1937-1939 (Box 375)
  - K-O, 1937-1939 (Box 376)
  - P-V, 1937-1939 (Box 377)
  - W-Z, 1937-1939 (Box 378)
- Series 2. Subject Files, 1931-1939; T001169
  - 1931-1933
    - Addresses (Box 379)
    - Aeronautics Advisory Board (Box 379)
    - Aeroplane Accident, Newington (Box 379)
    - Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 379)
    - American Legion (Box 379)
    - American Legislators' Association (Box 379)
    - Appointments (Direct) (Box 379)
    - Athletic Commission (Box 379)
    - Attorney General (Box 379)
    - Aviation (Box 379)
    - Bank Commissioner (Box 379)
    - Barbers, Board of Examiners (Box 379)
    - Boy Scouts of America (Box 379)
    - Campaign of 1932 (Box 379)
    - Chamber of Commerce, [Connecticut] (Box 379)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Hartford (Box 379)
    - Chemists, State (Box 379)
    - Child Welfare Bureau (Box 379)
    - Child Welfare Commission (Box 379)
    - Coast Guard Academy, New London (Box 379)
    - Communist Party (Box 379)
    - Compensation Commissioner (Box 379)
    - Comptroller's Office (Box 379)
    - Congress, Appeal to (Box 379)
    - Conn. College for Women (Box 380)
    - Conn. Geological & Natural History Survey (Box 380)
    - Conn. Reformatory, Cheshire (Box 380)
    - Conn. State College (Box 380)
    - Conn. State Hospital, Middletown (Box 380)
    - County Jails (Box 380)
    - Dairy & Food Commissioner (Box 380)
    - Danehower, Sloane, Lt. Cdr. - Sir Hubert Wilkins Expedition to the North (Box 380)
    - Congress, Appeal to (Box 380)
    - Deeds, Commissioner of (Box 380)
    - Direct Court Act SB 118 (Box 380)
    - Domestic Animals, Commissioner on (Box 380)
    - Eastern States Exposition (Box 380)
    - Economic and Financial Questions, Advisory Council on (Box 380)
    - Education, State Board of (Box 380)
    - Education of the Blind, State Board of (Box 380)
    - Election Acceptances (Box 380)
    - Embalmers, State Board of Examiners (Box 380)
    - Emergency Committee for, 4 folders (Box 380)
    - Emergency Relief Construction Act (Box 381)
    - Expenditures, Letter to State Agencies re (Box 381)
    - Fairfield State Hospital (Box 381)
    - Farmers' National Association, Inc. (Box 381)
    - Finance and Control, Board of (Box 381)
    - Fisheries and Game, State Board (Box 381)
    - Emergency Relief Construction Act (Box 381)
    - Forests and Wild Life, Commission on (Box 381)
    - Emergency Relief Construction Act (Box 381)
    - Fort Griswold Tract Commission (Box 381)
    - General Assembly (Box 381)
    - George Washington 200th Anniversary Celebration (Box 381)
    - Governors' Conference, 1931 (Box 381)
    - Governors' Conference, 1932 (Box 381)
    - Groton Heights and the Burning of New London Sesquicentennial, 1931 September 6-7 (Box 381)
    - Harbormasters (Box 381)
    - Health Department (Box 381)
    - Highway Department (Box 381)
    - Inauguration, F. D. Roosevelt (Box 381)
    - Insurance Commissioner (Box 381)
    - Judgeship Controversy (Box 381)
    - Judgeship Controversy (Box 381)
    - Labor Department (Box 381)
    - Life Insurance Presidents, Association of (Box 381)
    - Long Lane Farm, Middletown (Box 381)
    - Mansfield Training School & Hospital (Box 381)
    - Manufacturers' Association of Conn., Inc. (Box 381)
    - Medical Center (Box 381)
    - Meriden School for Boys (Box 381)
    - Metropolitan District Commission (Box 381)
    - Military (Box 381)
    - Milk Controversy (Box 382)
    - Mortgages, Interest Reduction on (Box 382)
    - Motor Vehicles Department (Box 382)
    - Mystic Oral School (Box 382)
    - New England Council (Box 382)
    - New England Railroad Committee (Box 382)
    - New Haven Hospital (Box 382)
    - Newington Home for Crippled Children (Box 382)
    - Norwich State Hospital (Box 382)
    - Notaries Public, 1931 (Box 382)
    - Nurses, Conn. Board of Examination and Registration (Box 382)
    - Pardons, Board of, 3 folders (Box 382)
    - Pension Commission (Box 382)
    - Portrait of the Governor (Box 382)
    - Press Matters (Box 382)
    - Prison Reform (Box 382)
    - Proclamations and Statements (Box 382)
    - Prohibition (Box 382)
    - Public Utilities Commission (Box 382)
    - Public Utilities Legislation (Box 382)
    - Public Welfare Department (Box 382)
    - Puerto Rico Child Feeding Committee, Inc. (Box 382)
    - Railroad Policemen (Box 383)
    - Reapportionment of Conn. Representatives in Congress (Box 383)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation (Box 383)
    - Relief Surveys - Angus P. Thorne (Box 383)
    - Requisitions (Box 383)
    - Rivers, Harbors & Bridges Commission (Box 383)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, Appeals to (Box 383)
    - Roton Point Park (Box 383)
    - Sculpture, Commission on (Box 383)
    - Siegman, Arthur, Inc. (Box 383)
    - Standard Electrical Time Company, Springfield, Mass. (Box 383)
    - State Agencies & Institutions, Department of (Box 383)
    - State Farm for Women (Box 383)
    - State Fund Committee - Captain E.P. Armstrong (Box 383)
    - State Highways, Sidewalks on (Box 383)
    - State Library (Box 383)
    - State Park & Forest Commission (Box 383)
    - State Police (Box 383)
    - State Prison Investigation (Box 383)
    - State Treasurer (Box 383)
    - State's Attorneys (Box 383)
    - Tax Department (Box 383)
    - Tax Information by Town obtained for Representative Lonergan (Box 383)
    - Teachers' Retirement Board (Box 383)
    - Tilson, Congressman, Resignation of (Box 383)
    - Trade Union Utility League (Box 383)
    - Tuberculosis Commission (Box 383)
    - Unemployment Commission Advisory Committee (Box 383)
    - Unemployment Insurance (Box 384)
    - United States Senate (Box 384)
    - Veterans Administration, Veterans Hospital, Newington (Box 384)
    - Water Commission (Box 384)
    - Waterways Purification, Tri-State Conference (Box 384)
    - Wesleyan University (Box 384)
    - Wethersfield State Prison (Box 384)
    - Yorktown Sesquicentennial Association (Box 384)
  - 1933-1935 (Box 384)
    - Addresses (Box 384)
    - Aeronautics Department (Box 384)
    - Agricultural Department (Box 384)
    - American Legion (Box 384)
    - Appointments (Direct) (Box 384)
    - Architects, Board of Examiners of (Box 384)
    - Athletic Department (Box 384)
    - Attorney General (Box 384)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 384)
    - Automobile, Governor's (Box 384)
    - Aviation Commission (Box 384)
    - Banking Commission (Box 384)
    - Barbers' Commission (Box 384)
    - Billboard Regulations (Box 384)
    - Bridgeport Armory Commission (Box 384)
    - Bridgeport, City of (Box 384)
    - Bristol, City of (Box 384)
    - Campaign (Box 384)
    - Campaign Addresses (Box 384)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Mr. Hasty (Box 384)
    - Chemists, State (Box 385)
    - Chicago Centennial Celebration (Box 385)
    - Chiropractic Examiners, State Board of (Box 385)
    - Civil Works Administration (Box 385)
    - Compensation Commissioner (Box 385)
    - Comptroller, State (Box 385)
    - Conn. Agricultural College - Committee to Consider Changes in name (Box 385)
    - Conn. College for Women (Box 385)
    - Conn. Humane Society (Box 385)
    - Conn. State College (Box 385)
    - County Jails (Box 385)
    - Dairy and Food Commissioner (Box 385)
    - Dental Commission (Box 385)
    - Domestic Animals, Commissioner of (Box 385)
    - East Hartford Sesquicentennial (Box 385)
    - Eclectic Medical Examining Board (Box 385)
    - Education, Board of (Box 385)
    - Eliphalet Nott Memorial Highway (Box 385)
    - Embalmers, State Board of Examiners of (Box 385)
    - Fairfield State Hospital (Box 385)
    - FERA (Federal Emergency Relief Administration) (Box 385)
    - Federal Relief Act (Box 385)
    - Feeble-minded, Additional Institutions for (Box 386)
    - Finance and Control, Board of (Box 386)
    - Fisheries and Game, State Board of (Box 386)
    - Fort Griswold and Groton Monument Commission (Box 386)
    - General Assembly (Box 386)
    - General Assembly, Special Session for the Construction of the Merritt Parkway (Box 386)
    - Geodetic Control Survey (Box 386)
    - Geological and Natural History Survey (Box 386)
    - Geological and Natural History Survey (Box 386)
    - Governors' Conference, 1933 (Box 386)
    - Governors' Conference, 1934 (Box 386)
    - Governor's Staff (Box 386)
    - Hairdressers and Cosmeticians Commission (Box 386)
    - Harbormasters (Box 386)
    - Healing Arts, State Board (Box 386)
    - Health Department (Box 386)
    - Highway Department (Box 386)
    - Home Loan Act (Box 386)
    - Homeopathic Medical Examining Board (Box 387)
    - Horticultural Society (Box 387)
    - Inaugural Address (Box 387)
    - Indian Medicine Man (Box 387)
    - Insurance Commission (Box 387)
    - Insurance Commission (Box 387)
    - Interstate Compact on Minimum Wage (Box 387)
    - Invitations Accepted (Box 387)
    - Invitations Regretted, 1933 June-December (Box 387)
    - Invitations Regretted, 1934 January (Box 387)
    - Jails, Report of Legislative Commission (Box 387)
    - Jews in Germany - Protest (Box 387)
    - Judgeship Controversy (Box 387)
    - Judgeships (Box 387)
    - Judicial Council (Box 387)
    - Labor Department (Box 387)
    - Labor Laws, Uniform (Box 387)
    - Liquor Control Bill (Box 387)
    - Liquor Control Clippings (Box 387)
    - Liquor Control Commission (Box 387)
    - Liquor Control - Special Session (Box 387)
    - Long Lane Farm (Box 387)
    - McNeil, Archibald (Box 388)
    - Maloney, Honorable Francis T. (Box 388)
    - Mansfield Training School and Hospital (Box 388)
    - Manufacturers Association of Conn. (Box 388)
    - Mediation and Arbitration Board (Box 388)
    - Medical Examining Board (Box 388)
    - Meriden School for Boys (Box 388)
    - Merritt Highway (Box 388)
    - Metropolitan District Commission (Box 388)
    - Middletown State Hospital (Box 388)
    - Military (Box 388)
    - Milk Control (Box 388)
    - Motor Vehicle Commissioner (Box 388)
    - Motor Vehicle Complaints (Box 388)
    - Motor Vehicle Department (Box 388)
    - Municipal Finance and Unemployment Relief Commission (Box 388)
    - Mystic Oral School (Box 388)
    - National Legislation (Box 388)
    - National Recovery Act (Box 389)
    - National Recovery Administration - Finance Committee (Box 389)
    - Naturopathic Examiners' Board (Box 389)
    - Naval Base, New London - Protest Closing (Box 389)
    - New England Council (Box 389)
    - New England Railroad Commission (Box 389)
    - Newington Home for Crippled Children (Box 389)
    - Newington Home Investigation (Box 389)
    - Norwich, Deputy Judge (Box 389)
    - Norwich State Hospital (Box 389)
    - Notary Public (Box 389)
    - Nurses, Examination and Registration of (Box 389)
    - Old Age Pension (Box 389)
    - Old Age Pension Commission (Box 389)
    - Optometric Society (Box 389)
    - Pardons, Board of (Box 389)
    - Pardons, Board of, Meetings, 3 folders (Box 389)
    - Pardons, Board of - Meetings, 1 folder (Box 390)
    - Park and Forest Commission (Box 390)
    - Pension, State (Box 390)
    - Pharmacy Commission (Box 390)
    - Plymouth (Town) Protest Bill (Box 390)
    - President's Reemployment Agreement (Box 390)
    - Press Matters (Box 390)
    - Proclamations (Box 390)
    - Prohibition (Box 390)
    - Protest - Unemployment Insurance (Box 390)
    - Public Utilities Commission (Box 390)
    - Public Welfare Department (Box 390)
    - Public Works Bill (Box 390)
    - Publicity, State Departments (Box 390)
    - Putnam Park Commission (Box 390)
    - Radio Legislation (Box 390)
    - Real Estate (Suggestions) (Box 390)
    - Reconstruction Finance corporation (Box 390)
    - Reforestation (Box 390)
    - Repeal Convention Luncheon (Box 390)
    - Repeal of 18th Amendment (Box 390)
    - Requesting Positions (Box 390)
    - Requisitions (Box 390)
    - Resignations (Box 390)
    - Rivers, Harbors & Bridges Commission (Box 390)
    - Sculpture Commission (Box 390)
    - Secretary of State (Box 390)
    - Senate (Box 390)
    - Senate Commendations - Governor's Stands (Box 390)
    - Shellfish Commission (Box 390)
    - Special Commission (Box 390)
    - Stamford Teachers' Tenure Bill (Box 390)
    - State Agencies and Institutions (Box 390)
    - State Departments - Reorganization (Box 390)
    - State Employment Service, Advisory Council on (Box 391)
    - State Farm for Women (Box 391)
    - State fund, Capt. Armstrong (Box 391)
    - State Library (Box 391)
    - State Liquor Commission - Injunction (Box 391)
    - State Planning Board (Box 391)
    - State Police Dept. (Box 391)
    - State Recovery Board (Box 391)
    - State Reformatory, Cheshire (Box 391)
    - State Teachers' Association (Box 391)
    - State's Attorney (Box 391)
    - Supreme Court (Box 391)
    - Tax Department (Box 391)
    - Tax Study Committee (Box 391)
    - Tax Survey, Judge Mink (Box 391)
    - Taxation Suggestions (Box 391)
    - Taxes, Collection of (Box 391)
    - Tercentenary Commission, 3 folders (Box 391)
    - Textile Strike (Box 391)
    - Treasury Department (Box 392a)
    - Truck Strike (Box 392a)
    - Tuberculosis Commission (Box 392a)
    - Unemployment (Mr. Neithercut) (Box 392a)
    - Unemployment Commission, 2 folders (Box 392a)
    - Unemployment Commission, Advisory Committee (Box 392a)
    - Unemployment Relief, State Aid for (Box 392a)
    - Veterans Home Commission (Box 392b)
    - Veterinary Examining Board (Box 392b)
    - Voting Machine Commission (Box 392b)
    - Water Commission (Box 392b)
    - Weber Dam Investigation, 2 folders (Box 392b)
    - Wethersfield State Prison (Box 392b)
  - 1935-1937
    - Accident Prevention Conference (Box 393)
    - Accountancy, State Board of (Box 393)
    - Addresses (Box 393)
    - Aeronautics Department (Box 393)
    - Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 393)
    - American Academy of Political and Social Science (Box 393)
    - American Historical Association, Inc. (Box 393)
    - American Industrial Parade Assoc. (Box 393)
    - American Legion (Box 393)
    - American National Committee (Box 393)
    - American Public Welfare Association (Box 393)
    - Architects, Board of Examiners (Box 393)
    - Armory Board (Box 393)
    - Association for the Preservation of Antiquities (Box 393)
    - Attorney General (Box 393)
    - Automobiles - Statute Forbidding Repair and Sale on Sunday, Protests (Box 393)
    - Bank Commission (Box 393)
    - Bank Commissioner, Advisory Council (Box 393)
    - Barber Commission (Box 393)
    - Birthday Ball Presidents (Box 393)
    - Black Legion - Protests (Box 393)
    - Boy Scouts of America (Box 393)
    - Bridgeport Centennial (Box 393)
    - Budget (Box 393)
    - Chemist, State (Box 393)
    - Child Welfare Commission (Box 393)
    - Chiropractic Examiners, State Board of (Box 393)
    - Citron, William M., Congressman (Box 393)
    - Civil Service Reform (Box 393)
    - Clippings, Legislature (Box 393)
    - Clippings, Newspaper Miscellaneous (Box 393)
    - Compensation Commissioner (Box 393)
    - Comptroller (Box 393)
    - Congratulations on Renominations (Box 393)
    - Conn. College for Women (Box 393)
    - Conn. College for Women - Meeting, Board of Trustees (Box 393)
    - Conn. College for Women - Statement of Receipts and Disbursements (Box 393)
    - Conn. Prison Association (Box 393)
    - Conn. River Bridge, Middletown (Box 393)
    - Conn. State College (Box 393)
    - Conn. State College - Minutes of Meeting (Box 394)
    - Conn. State College - News Bulletin (Box 394)
    - Conn. State College, Actions of Board of Trustees - Protest (Box 394)
    - Constellation (U.S.S.) (Box 394)
    - Council of State Governments and American Legislators' Association (2 organizations) (Box 394)
    - Dairy and Food Commission (Box 394)
    - Dental Commissioners (Box 394)
    - Domestic Animals Commission (Box 394)
    - Dragon (H.M.S.) (Box 394)
    - Eastern Conn. Commission (Box 394)
    - Edison (Thomas Alva) Commission (Box 394)
    - Education, Board of (Box 394)
    - Education of the Blind, Board of (Box 394)
    - Election (Box 394)
    - Embalmers, Examiners of (Box 394)
    - Employment Service, Advisory Council of (Box 394)
    - Emergency Relief Commission (Box 394)
    - Emergency Relief Commission - Minutes of Meeting (Box 394)
    - Engineers and Land Surveyors, Board of Registration of (Box 394)
    - Fairfield State Hospital (Box 394)
    - Farmington River Bridge, New Hartford (Box 394)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 394)
    - Federal Emergency Relief Act (Box 394)
    - Feeble-Minded, New Home for (Box 394)
    - Finance and Control (Box 395)
    - Financial Responsibility Act, Study Commission for (Box 395)
    - Fisheries and Game (Box 395)
    - Fitch's Home for Soldiers (Box 395)
    - Fitzgerald, David E. (Box 395)
    - Flood (Box 395)
    - Flood Relief Fund (Box 395)
    - Flood Reports (Box 395)
    - Forest and Park Association (Box 395)